We’re sorry, but our website doesn’t work properly without JavaScript enabled. Please enable JavaScript in order to continue using our website.

           Privacy Policy                                    

Products Education 

Popular Searches
----------------

Applied

Popular on PetMeds
------------------

50% Off\* Flea, Tick, and Heartworm essentials with AutoShip. Code: SHIELD50[Shop Now](https://www.1800petmeds.com/save-on-flea-tick-heartworm-promo240402.html?campaign=shield50_protect30_promo)

MENU CLOSE

Products Education 

Popular Searches
----------------

Popular on PetMeds
------------------

  Swipe

Applied

Back

Close ×

    * Categories
        
    * Categories

    Categories

    Categories

    Categories

    Categories

    Categories

    Categories

    Categories

    Categories

        Categories

Navigation [×](javascript:void(0))

SAVE AN EXTRA $5 - $20 OFFUse code PETS in cart ([Exclusions apply](https://www.1800petmeds.com/tc.html))

Save 40% with first AutoShipUse code NEW40 (Up to $40 max. [Exclusions apply](https://www.1800petmeds.com/tc.html))

[

2% Back on all PurchasesWith PetMeds® Rewards Program](https://www.1800petmeds.com/loyalty-program.html?utm_source=homepage&utm_medium=bar_vp&utm_campaign=rewards_program)

Who We Are

* * *

* * *

* * *

**Privacy Policy**
==================

At PetMed Express, Inc., dba PetMeds® (collectively, "we," "us," "our," or "PetMeds"), we value your personal privacy. This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") describes how we collect, use, share, disclose, store, and safeguard personal information. This Privacy Policy also tells you about your rights and choices with respect to your personal information, and how you can reach us to get answers to your questions. By using or accessing our website, mobile application and other online products and services, shop in our online store, contact our customer service team, or otherwise interact with us, you agree to the collection, storage, use and disclosure of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

**WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT**
-------------------------------

When you purchase something from our online store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you voluntarily give us such as your name, billing and shipping address, telephone or mobile number, email address, age, gender, location, your pet’s information (name, breed, date of birth, gender, etc.), call recording and chat transcript data from sales and support calls and live chat/SMS sessions, and order history. We also use tracking tools including cookies, web beacons or other online information-gathering tools that collect information that make it easier to use our online store and our website. We also partner with third-party advertising companies which may use cookies to provide banner advertisements about products and services of interest to you.

When you visit our website, some information is automatically collected. This may include information such as the Operating System (OS) running on your device, Internet Protocol (IP) address (which may be used to obtain your geolocation), access date and time, browser type, language, and the website you visited before our website. We also collect information about how you use our website, including click-activity, the elements you have interacted with, metadata and other details about these elements, change states and other user actions.

When you participate in a survey, we collect information that you provide through the survey. When you rate or review us or our products, we collect any information you provide as part of that rating or review.

By providing us with your email address, you are giving us permission to send you emails about our products and services, new products, new brands and other updates, and to notify you of your order status and when it is time to re-order your pet's medication or other products. Occasionally PetMeds will have promotions or special offers which we feel you may benefit from and we will send you a notice. You have the opportunity to unsubscribe from these emails at any time simply by emailing [optout@1800petmeds.com](mailto:optout@1800petmeds.com) or by clicking the ”Unsubscribe” link included at the bottom of each email that you may receive from PetMeds. You can also opt out online by using the following link: [Email Preferences](https://www.1800petmeds.com/email-preferences) and entering your email address.

PetMeds does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under 18 years of age. If we learn that PetMeds has inadvertently gathered personal Information from children under 18 years of age, we will take all reasonable measures to promptly delete such Information.

**HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**
-------------------------------

In general, we use the information we collect primarily to provide the products, services and information you request, customize your experience with us, provide, maintain, protect and improve our current website and products, support our business functions (such as order fulfillment, internal business process management, marketing, authentication, loss and fraud prevention, and public safety functions), conduct contests, surveys, market research, and data analytics, and to communicate with you about our product offers and promotions. We may use your information in other ways, which we will give specific notice of at your time of concent. When you create an account with us, we offer the opportunity to become a member of PetMeds Rewards Program, so you may earn future credits and receive member-only specials, exclusive offers, and advance notice of sales, special events and flash sales. We may retain your data for as long as we believe there is a business, legal or security reason for doing so, even if you are no longer an active customer.

**WHAT INFORMATION WE DISCLOSE**
--------------------------------

We do not share your personal information with third parties without your consent other than with the following:

* Third Party Service Providers. With third parties who work on our behalf, including among other things service providers who may help us to administer our website, collect data for analysis purposes, conduct surveys, provide technical support, process payments, provide marketing research and assistance (including email and mobile marketing), deliver packages, and assist in the fulfillment of orders;
  
* Vetster for fulfillment of our VetLive telehealth/telemedicine service. If you utilize our VetLive service we will share your information with our partner, Vetster, for fulfillment of the service. Their privacy policy will apply and is available at [Privacy Policy - Vetster](https://vetster.com/en-us/legal/privacy) ;
  
* Pumpkin Insurance Services Inc. (“Pumpkin”) for fulfillment of pet insurance needs. If you utilize the services of our fully licensed insurance broker, PetMeds Insurance Services, LLC, for pet insurance products, then we will share your information with Pumpkin, our partner for obtaining insurance quotes. Pumpkin’s privacy policy will apply to all your information we, or you, provide to them and is available at [Privacy Policy](https://www.pumpkin.care/privacy-center/privacy-policy/) ;
  
* Veterinary Care Providers or Pharmaceutical Product Manufacturers. If you use pharmacy services available through our services and/or fulfilled by us, the pharmacy may share your and/or your pet's information with veterinary care providers to validate prescriptions or provide other advice. The pharmacy also may share such information with pharmaceutical manufacturers if so doing will among other things help facilitate the treatment of your pet or provide required adverse event information to the manufacturer;
  
* Affiliates and Subsidiaries. We may share your information with our affiliates and subsidiaries for business, operational, promotional, marketing or other purposes consistent with our Privacy Policy;
  
* With the Public. We share your information with the public if you post information online and elect to make it available to the public, such as by writing a product review on our website;
  
* Lawful Requests. To comply with laws or to respond to lawful requests and legal process, including subpoenas, warrants, court orders, or in connection with any legal process (provided that we will endeavor to notify you at the address you have given us if we have received a lawful request for your information);
  
* Protection of Rights and Property. To protect the rights and property of PetMeds, our agents, customers and others including to enforce our agreements, policies and terms included in this Privacy Policy;
  
* Emergency. In an emergency, including to protect the personal safety of any person or pet; and
  
* Corporate Restructuring. For the purposes of a business deal (or negotiation of a business deal) involving a sale or transfer of all or a part of our business or assets (business deals may include, for example, any merger, financing, acquisition, divestiture or dissolution transaction or proceeding). In the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership, personal information may also be transferred as a business asset. If another company acquires our company, business or assets, that company will also acquire and possess the personal information collected by us and will assume the rights and obligations regarding your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We may also share aggregated or de-identified information that cannot reasonably be used to identify you.

**PAYMENT PROCESSING**
----------------------

Our online store is built on an e-commerce software platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you. If you provide payment details to us, we send these details to PCI-DSS compliant 3rd party fraud verification services, and our payment gateway, using secure connection and transmission encryption technology. Your credit card information is stored for recurring subscription orders as well as within your account for faster checkout experience.

All direct payment gateways comply with the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our online store and our payment processors and service providers.

**DATA SECURITY**
-----------------

Protecting your personal information is important to us. While we work to protect your information, a breach may still happen. In the event of a breach that we are required by law to inform you of, we may notify you electronically, in writing, or by telephone, if permitted to do so by law.

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow generally accepted industry practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed. Your personal information is protected by your password – never share this password with anyone. PetMeds will never contact you to ask you for your password. In addition, please note that we do not control the communication channel you choose to communicate with us and cannot guarantee secure information transmission.

**FINANCIAL INFORMATION/ONLINE PAYMENT SECURITY**
-------------------------------------------------

PetMeds guarantees that every online transaction you make will be 100% safe. This means you pay nothing if unauthorized charges are made to your card as a result of shopping at our online store. Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50.00 of fraudulent charges. If your bank does hold you liable for any of this $50.00, we will cover this entire liability for you, up to the full $50.00. We will only cover this liability if the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases made at [1800petmeds.com](https://www.1800petmeds.com/) while using the secure server. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.

**MOBILE PRIVACY**
------------------

PetMeds offers mobile applications that allow you to shop online, check product information, or receive other information from PetMeds. Personal information collected from your mobile device is protected as described in this Privacy Policy. Our applications or our third party service providers may automatically collect information about your precise location from your device, but only if you allow it.

We use your location information to enhance your shopping experience. You may at any time adjust the permissions in your mobile device to opt-out from allowing PetMeds mobile applications access to your device’s camera and or location information. You can opt out from further allowing PetMeds to send you push notifications by adjusting the permissions in your mobile device or from the app.

You can prospectively stop all collection of information by the mobile application by uninstalling the application. If you use the service through an Apple, Inc. ("Apple") device, we may offer Touch ID or Face ID as an alternative log-in method to password. We are only notified as to whether the authentication was successful and cannot access Touch ID, Face ID or the data associated with the enrolled fingerprint. For more details, see [Apple's iOS Security Guide](https://www.apple.com/business/docs/iOS_Security_Guide.pdf).

**PETMEDS SMS PROGRAM TERMS**
-----------------------------

1. By joining PetMeds SMS program, you expressly consent to receive recurring text messages from PetMeds on new deals, PetMeds promotional offers and cart reminder messages. Your consent is not a condition for purchase of any goods or services. Message frequency varies. Message and data rates may apply.
2. You can cancel the SMS service at any time. Just text "STOP" to the short code. After you send the SMS message "STOP" to us, we will send you an SMS message to confirm that you have been unsubscribed. After this, you will no longer receive SMS messages from us. If you want to join again, just sign up as you did the first time and we will start sending SMS messages to you again.
3. If you are experiencing issues with the messaging program you can reply with the keyword HELP for more assistance, or you can get help directly at 1-800-738-6337.
4. Carriers are not liable for delayed or undelivered messages
5. As always, message and data rates may apply for any messages sent to you from us and to us from you. Message frequency varies. If you have any questions about your text plan or data plan, it is best to contact your wireless provider.
6. For information on privacy, please read the rest of our Privacy Policy above/below.

###### WHAT INFORMATION WE DISCLOSE:

All the above categories exclude text messaging originator opt-in data and consent; this information will not be shared with any third parties for their own marketing reasons.

We use Cookies and local storage to capture commercial information for products viewed or added to your shopping cart as well. Cookies will also help us determine if the shopping cart is abandoned to send you shopping cart reminders messages.

**MAILING LIST**
----------------

When you make a purchase or register an account, you are automatically enrolled in our mailing lists, or you may request that we add you to our mailing list. If at any time you do not want to receive offers and/or circulars from us you can remove yourself from our mailing lists by emailing us at [customerservice@1800petmeds.com](mailto:customerservice@1800petmeds.com) with "NO GROUND MAIL" in the subject line along with your name, and address. Please note that our mailings are prepared in advance of their being sent. Although we will remove your name from our mailing list after receiving your request, you may still receive mailings from us that had been initiated prior to your name being removed.

**THIRD-PARTY APPLICATIONS/WEBSITES**
-------------------------------------

When you click on links on our online store, they may direct you away from our website. In addition, our website may offer social sharing features and other integrated tools (such as the Facebook "Like" button), which let you share actions you take on our website with other media. Your use of such features enables the sharing of information with your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with the entity that provides the social sharing feature. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any third party services or entities that provide social sharing features except as described in this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for and have no control over the privacy practices of other websites or applications that we do not own. To learn about those third parties' privacy practices, please read their privacy policies.

**U.S. LAW APPLIES**
--------------------

Our website is intended for users located in the United States. By sending us your personal information from outside the U.S., you consent to the application of U.S. law and to the use and disclosure of your personal information consistent with this Privacy Policy. It is up to you to determine whether accessing our website and purchasing our products are legal where you are. You access our website and purchase our products at your own risk, and you are responsible for compliance with all applicable laws, rules, regulations and treaties. Further, by choosing to visit our online store, you agree that any dispute over privacy or the terms contained in this Privacy Policy will be governed by the law of the State of Florida, without reference to the choice of law or conflicts of law principles thereof.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**
----------------------------------

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the bottom of this Privacy Policy, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on our website. PetMeds encourages you to check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy whenever you access the website or otherwise interact with us.

**WANT FURTHER INFORMATION?**
-----------------------------

If you would like to access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you (other than that information automatically generated by your use of our website), register a complaint, or simply want more information contact, please contact us at PetMed Express, Inc., attn: Privacy Officer, 420 South Congress Avenue, Delray Beach, Florida 33445, or email us at [customerservice@1800petmeds.com](mailto:%20customerservice@1800petmeds.com) or call us toll-free at [1-800-PetMeds](#) (1-800-738-6337).

**ACCESSIBILITY**
-----------------

Accessibility, diversity and inclusion are important values at PetMeds. It is the goal of PetMeds and its affiliates for our website and mobile application to be accessible to all. We are continually working to conform our website, to the extent possible, to the standards set out in the Web Content Accessibility Guidelines (WCAG) or other standards to the extent required by the Americans with Disabilities Act ("ADA"). Please be aware that our efforts are ongoing. If, at any time, you have specific questions or concerns about the accessibility of any particular page on our website or if you have any difficulty accessing or using our website, please email us at [customerservice@1800petmeds.com](mailto:customerservice@1800petmeds.com) or call us toll-free at [1-800-PetMeds](#) (1-800-738-6337). We will make all reasonable efforts to work with you to identify the issue and make our website accessible to you.

**NEVADA PRIVACY RIGHTS**
-------------------------

Under Nevada law, certain Nevada consumers may opt out of the “sale” of “personally identifiable information” as such terms are defined under Nevada law. We do not engage in such activity; however, if you are a Nevada resident who has purchased goods or services from us, you may submit a request to opt out of any potential future sales under Nevada law by contacting us at [customerservice@1800petmeds.com](mailto:customerservice@1800petmeds.com) or call us toll-free at [1-800-PetMeds](#) (1-800-738-6337). We will take reasonable steps to verify your identity and the authenticity of the request. Once verified, we will maintain your request in the event our practices change.

**CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**
-----------------------------

Consumers residing in California have certain additional rights with respect to their personal information under the California Consumer Privacy Act ("CCPA") and the "Shine the Light" Law. The California “Shine the Light” law gives residents of California the right under certain circumstances to request information from us regarding the manner in which we share certain categories of personal information (as defined in the Shine the Light law) with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. We do not share your personal information with third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. The CCPA provides California residents with the right to not be discriminated against (as provided for in applicable law) for exercising rights to access and delete your personal information. As a California resident, you have the right to request a report of the information we collect about you, from whom it has been obtained, and the categories of business with which we share the information. This information is provided in this Privacy Policy in the sections above.

You have the right to request:

* The specific categories of personal information we have collected about you during the previous 12 months;
  
* The specific personal information we have collected about you during the previous 12 months, depending upon verification of your identity or verification of the person authorized to act on your behalf;
  
* The categories of personal information we have disclosed to third parties about you along with the categories of the organizations receiving that information during the previous 12 months;
  
* The deletion of your personal information, subject to several exemptions available to us.

Please note that PetMeds does not sell personal information or customer data regardless of the state in which the customer resides.

California residents may request a report of their personal information collected by us and how it has been used and shared with third parties, or request data deletion by emailing us at [customerservice@1800petmeds.com](mailto:%20customerservice@1800petmeds.com) or call us toll-free at [1-800-PetMeds](#) (1-800-738-6337).

For additional information concerning CCPA, please send a detailed email to [ccpa@1800petmeds.com](mailto:ccpa@1800petmeds.com).

To opt out of email communications or the use of data at a browser level, you may make your selections [here](https://www.1800petmeds.com/email-preferences).

Prior to honoring your request, the Company will make a reasonable attempt to verify your identity. You may designate an authorized agent to make a request not to disclose or to delete your personal information by providing the authorized agent written permission to do so and by verifying your own identity with us. The Company will not discriminate against you if you take advantage of these rights.

Last updated February 13, 2024

Contact Us
----------

Toll Free Number (Call or [Text](sms:18007386337)):

1-800-PetMeds®

Due to unusually high call volumes, we are experiencing longer wait times. We sincerely apologize, and thank you for your patience.

Mailing Address:

420 S Congress Ave. #100  
Delray Beach, FL 33445

\*If your pet is in need of urgent or emergency care, contact your pet's veterinarian immediately.

### Company Info

#### [Company Info](#collapse1)

### Customer Service

#### [Customer Service](#collapse2)

### PetMeds® Programs

#### [PetMeds® Programs](#collapse3) 

### PetMeds® Partnerships

#### [PetMeds® Partnerships](#collapse4) 

### Verified Pet Pharmacy

Copyright © 2024 PetMed Express, Inc. All Rights Reserved. [Comparison Sitemap](https://www.1800petmeds.com/comparison-sitemap). [Exclusions](https://www.1800petmeds.com/on/demandware.store/Sites-1800petmeds-Site/default/tc) page.
